<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">PasswordLocker</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="need_help">Need Help?</string>
    <string name="enter_password_hint">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="confirm_password_hint">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="hint_hint">Add Your Hint</string>
    <string name="bt_enter">Enter</string>
    <string name="btn_save">Save</string>
    <string name="dial_title_create_pass">Create Password</string>
    <string name="pos_btn_crea_pass">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="neg_btn_crea_pass">Create For Me</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="copy">Copy</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="label">LabelLabel</string>
    <string name="invalid">Invalid</string>
    <string name="poor">poor</string>
    <string name="weak">weak</string>
    <string name="good">good</string>
    <string name="strong">StrongS</string>
    <string name="add_acount">Add Account</string>
    <string name="hint_enter_account">Enter Account</string>
    <string name="label_new_account">New Account</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>


    <string name="need_help_tutorial1">We touched on cryptography very briefly in Chapter 4. This
        chapter will focus more on the importance of using cryptography to obfuscate and secure
        user data that you will either store or transport. First, we will cover the basics of
        cryptography and how they apply to us in the context of application development. Next,
        we will look at the various mechanisms of storing data on the Android platform.</string>

    <string name="need_help_tutorial2">
        Along the way, I will give examples of how to store and retrieve data from different
        mechanisms and outline what function each store is ideally suited toperform.</string>

    <string name="need_help_tutorial3">
        One very important point to keep in mind is you should never attempt to write your own
        cryptographic routines unless you are familiar with cryptographic topics.</string>

    <string name="need_help_tutorial4">
        I have seen many developers try to do this and end up with vulnerable applications both
        on mobile devices and in web applications. Cryptography is a vast subject by itself;
        and, in my opinion, I think it is best left to the folks who dedicate their lives to
        the subject.</string>


    <string name="need_help_tutorial5">
        As an application developer, you will only be interested in a specific subset of topics in
        cryptography. I won’t cover the history of cryptography. You only need to keep one thing in
        mind: make your sensitive user data unreadable to unauthorized users.
        If an attacker compromises your application using either an indirect or direct attack,
        then your additional layer (see Figure 5-1) of cryptography will not make it trivial
        for him to steal the sensitive user data. Instead, he has an additional layer that he has
        to attack.</string>

    <string name="need_help_tutorial6">
        This principle is similar to the Information Assurance principle of Defense in Depth that
        the US National Security Agency developed.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <!--These string are keys used for preferences -->
    <string name="preferences_clipboard_minutes_key">CLIP_BOARD_MINUTES</string>
    <string name="pref_password_length">PREF_PASSWORD_LENGTH</string>
    <string name="title_activity_preferences">PreferencesActivity</string>




</resources>
